Historic Image Collection HIC
Stage
- Engraving and Printing, Bureau of
  See Also: Trees - Cherry
- Ethnic Groups
- Executive Office Building
  See Also: State, War and Navy Building
- Exhibitions
- Federal Aviation Agency
- Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI)
- Federal Reserve Board
- Federal Trade Commission
  See Also: Apex Building; See Also: Triangle
- Federal Triangle
  See: Triangle
- Ferries
- Fire Department
- Fires
- Fish Commission
- Fish Market
  See: Waterfront
- Fish Wharf
- Floods
  See Also: Canals - C And O; See Also: Potomac River - Floods; See Also: Weather
- Flowers and Flower Shows
- Foggy Bottom
  See Also: Residential Sections
- Folger Shakespeare Library
- Food Stamps
- Ford's Theater
  See: Theaters; See: Streets - 10th Street
- Forts
- Fountains
  See Also: Library of Congress; See Also: Union Station
- Franciscan Monastery
- Freer Gallery of Art
  See: Smithsonian Institution - Freer Gallery
- Funerals
- Funerals - Dirksen, Everett
- Funerals - Eisenhower, Dwight D.
- Funerals - Emery, Mathew G.
- Funerals - Harding, Warren G.
- Funerals - Hazen, Melvin C.
- Funerals - Hoover, Herbert
- Funerals - Kennedy, John F.
- Funerals - Lincoln, Abraham
- Funerals - MacArthur, Douglas
- Funerals - McKinley, William
- Funerals - Roosevelt, Franklin D.
- Funerals - Sailors from the USS Maine
- Funerals - Stevenson, Adlai
- Funerals - Taft, Robert A.
- Funerals - Unknown
- Funerals - Unknown Soldier
  See: Arlington National Cemetery - Tomb of the Unknown
- Funerals - Waite, Morrison
- Funerals - Walker, John G.
- Funerals - Washington, George
- Gallery Place
- Gambling
- Gardens
- Garfinkel's
  See: Stores - Garfinckel's
- Gas Company
- Gates and Gatehouse
- General Accounting Office
- General Stores
- Georgetown
  See: Reservoir; See: Residential Sections; See: Restaurants; See: Water Supply; See: Waterfront
- Glen Echo
  See: Metropolitan District
- Goodwill
- Government Auditorium
- Government Girls
  See: World War II - Women
- Government Printing Office
- Grand Army of the Republic (GAR)
- Great Falls
  See: Potomac River - Great Falls
- Grief
  See: Memorials - Adams, Henry
- Griffith Stadium
  See: Sports; See: Stadiums
- Hall of the Ancients
- Halls
- Halls, Masonic
- Health, Education and Welfare Department
- Heat and Power Plant
- Hecht Company
  See: Stores - Hecht Company
- Hirshhorn Museum and Sculpture Garden
  See: Museum - Hirshhorn
- History and Technology Museum
- Home Rule
  See: Politics and Government; See: Parades - Home Rule; See: Suffrage
- Homeless
- Hoover, J. Edgar Building
  See: Federal Bureau of Investigation
- Horse Car
- Horses
  See Also: Transportation
- Hospitals
- Hospitals - Armory Hospital
- Hospitals - Bethesda Naval Center
- Hospitals - Casualty Hospital
- Hospitals - Children's Hospital
- Hospitals - Civil War
- Hospitals - Columbia Hospital
- Hospitals - Douglas and Stanton Hospital
- Hospitals - Emergency Hospital
- Hospitals - Episcopal Eye, Ear and Throat Hospital
- Hospitals - Fort Myer
- Hospitals - Freedman's Hospital
- Hospitals - Gallinger Hospital
- Hospitals - Garfield Hospital
- Hospitals - George Washington University Hospital
- Hospitals - Georgetown University Hospital
- Hospitals - Glen Dale Sanitarium
- Hospitals - Homeopathic Hospital
- Hospitals - Lincoln Hospital
- Hospitals - Marine Hospital
- Hospitals - Military Hospital
- Hospitals - National Naval Medical Center (Bethesda)
- Hospitals - Naval Hospital
- Hospitals - Private Eye Hospital
- Hospitals - Providence Hospital
- Hospitals - Saint Elizabeth's Hospital
- Hospitals - Sibley Hospital
- Hospitals - Veterans Administration Hospital
- Hospitals - Walter Reed Army Medical Center
- Hospitals - Washington Hospital Center
- Hospitals - Washington Infirmary
- Hospitals - Washington Sanitarium
- Hotels
- Hotels - Amphitrite
- Hotels - Arlington Hotel
- Hotels - Arno Hotel
- Hotels - Blodgett's Hotel
- Hotels - Brock's Congressional Hotel
- Hotels - Brown's Marble Hotel
- Hotels - Brunswick Hotel
- Hotels - Cabin John Hotel
- Hotels - Cairo Hotel
- Hotels - Capitol Park Hotel
- Hotels - Carlton Hotel
- Hotels - Colonial Hotel
- Hotels - Columbia Hotel
- Hotels - Congressional Hotel
- Hotels - Dodge Hotel
- Hotels - Ebbitt House/Hotel
- Hotels - European Hotel
- Hotels - Fairfax Hotel
- Hotels - Franklin House
- Hotels - Fredonia Hotel
- Hotels - Fritz-Reuters Hotel
- Hotels - Gadsby's Tavern
- Hotels - George Washington House/Inn
- Hotels - Government House
- Hotels - Grafton Hotel
- Hotels - Great Hotel
  See: Blodgett's Hotel
- Hotels - Hamilton
- Hotels - Hotel Harrington
- Hotels - Indian Queen Tavern
- Hotels - International Inn
- Hotels - Kirkwood House
- Hotels - La Fetra's Hotel
- Hotels - Lafayette Hotel
- Hotels - Little Hotel
- Hotels - Long's Hotel
- Hotels - Lovell's Hotel
- Hotels - Marriott MarQuis
- Hotels - Mayflower Hotel
- Hotels - Meridian Hill Hotel
- Hotels - Metropolitan Hotel
- Hotels - Montrose Hotel
- Hotels - National Hotel
- Hotels - New Capital Hotel
- Hotels - Oxford Hotel
- Hotels - Palo Alto Hotel
- Hotels - Pickwick Inn
- Hotels - Portland Hotel
- Hotels - Potomac Hotel
- Hotels - Powhatan Hotel
- Hotels - Raleigh Hotel
- Hotels - Rhodes Hotel
  See: Lovell's Hotel
- Hotels - Rhodes Tavern
- Hotels - Richmond Hotel
- Hotels - Riggs Hotel
- Hotels - Roosevelt Hotel
- Hotels - St. Charles Hotel
- Hotels - St. James Hotel
- Hotels - Shepherd House
- Hotels - Sheraton-Carlton Hotel
- Hotels - Sheraton Park Hotel
- Hotels - Shoreham Hotel
- Hotels - Snow Tavern
- Hotels - Southern Hotel
- Hotels - Statler Hotel
- Hotels - Stelles Hotel
- Hotels - Stratford Hotel
- Hotels - Suter's Tavern
- Hotels - Thyson Hotel
- Hotels - Tunnicliff's Tavern
- Hotels - Union Tavern/Hotel
- Hotels - Vendome Hotel
- Hotels - Wardman Park Hotel
- Hotels - Washington Hilton
- Hotels - Washington Hotel
  See Also: Lovell's Hotel
- Hotels - West End Hotel
- Hotels - Willard Hotel
  See Also: Theaters - Stage Door Canteen; See Also: World War I; See Also: World War II - Service Clubs
- House Office Building
- House Office Building - Cannon
- House Office Building - Longworth
- House Office Building - Rayburn
- Houses
  See Also: Streets
- Houses - General
- Houses - Numbered Streets
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 1st Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 2nd Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 3rd Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 4th Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 6th Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 10th Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 11th Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 12th Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 13th Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 14th Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 15th Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 16th Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 17th Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 18th Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 20th Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 21st Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 22nd Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 23rd Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 24th Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 26th Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 27th Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 28th Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 29th Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 30th Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 31st Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 32nd Street
- Houses - Numbered Streets - 35th Street
- Houses - Named Streets
- Houses - Named Streets - A Street
- Houses - Named Streets - B Street
- Houses - Named Streets - C Street (Other)
- Houses - Named Streets - C Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Cathedral Street
- Houses - Named Streets - California Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Cambridge Road
- Houses - Named Streets - Cambridge Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Canal Road
- Houses - Named Streets - Chain Bridge Road
- Houses - Named Streets - Chesapeake Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Clifton Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Columbia Road
- Houses - Named Streets - Connecticut Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - Corcoran House
  See H Street
- Houses - Named Streets - D Street
- Houses - Named Streets - DC Village Lane
- Houses - Named Streets - Decatur Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Decatur House
  See Jackson Place
- Houses - Named Streets - Delaware Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - Dolly Madison House
  See Madison Place
- Houses - Named Streets - Douglas (Frederick) House
  See W Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Duddington Manor
  See 1st Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Dumbarton Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - Dumbarton Oaks
  See 32nd Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Dupont Circle
- Houses - Named Streets - E Street
- Houses - Named Streets - East Capitol Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Euclid Street
- Houses - Named Streets - F Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Fairmont Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Foxhall Road
- Houses - Named Streets - G Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Georgia Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - H Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Holt House
  See Adams Mill Road
- Houses - Named Streets - I Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Independence Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - Indiana Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - Jackson Hill
- Houses - Named Streets - Jackson Place
- Houses - Named Streets - K Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Kalorama Road
- Houses - Named Streets - Klingle Road
- Houses - Named Streets - L Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Lincoln Road
- Houses - Named Streets - Longfellow Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Lowell Street
- Houses - Named Streets - M Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Madison Place
- Houses - Named Streets - Mason House
- Houses - Named Streets - Massachusetts Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - Meihle Place
- Houses - Named Streets - N Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Nebraska Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - New Hampshire Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - New Jersey Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - New York Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - Newark Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Newton Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Normanstone Drive
- Houses - Named Streets - North Capitol Street
- Houses - Named Streets - North Carolina Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - O Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Ogden Place
- Houses - Named Streets - Old Stone House
  See: Houses - M Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Oregon Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - P Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Pennsylvania Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - Phelps Place
- Houses - Named Streets - Pomander Walk
- Houses - Named Streets - Potomac Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - Potomac Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Prospect Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - Q Street
- Houses - Named Streets - R Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Reservoir Road
- Houses - Named Streets - Rhode Island Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - Rock Creek Church Road
- Houses - Named Streets - S Street
- Houses - Named Streets - South Carolina Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - Southwest
- Houses - Named Streets - Surratsville, MD
- Houses - Named Streets - T Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Theodore Roosevelt Island
- Houses - Named Streets - Thomas Jefferson Street
- Houses - Named Streets - V Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Van Ness Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Vermont Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - Virginia Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - W Street
- Houses - Named Streets - Wisconsin Avenue
- Houses - Named Streets - Wyoming Avenue
- Housing
- Housing - Alleys
- Housing - Defense
- Housing - Group
- Housing - Model
- Housing - Slums
- Hurricanes
  See: Weather
- Ice Skating
- Inaugurations
- Inaugurations - Buchanan, James G.
- Inaugurations - Carter, James E.
- Inaugurations - Cleveland, Grover
- Inaugurations - Coolidge, Calvin
- Inaugurations - Eisenhower, Dwight D.
- Inaugurations - Garfield, James
- Inaugurations - Grant, Ulysses, S.
- Inaugurations - Harding, Warren
- Inaugurations - Harrison, William
- Inaugurations - Hayes, Rutherford B.
- Inaugurations - Hoover, Herbert
- Inaugurations - Jackson, Andrew
- Inaugurations - Jefferson, Thomas
- Inaugurations - Johnson, Lyndon B.
- Inaugurations - Kennedy, John F.
- Inaugurations - Lincoln, Abraham
- Inaugurations - McKinley, William
- Inaugurations - Obama, Barack
- Inaugurations - Pierce, Franklin
- Inaugurations - Polk, James K.
- Inaugurations - Roosevelt, Franklin D.
- Inaugurations - Roosevelt, Theodore
- Inaugurations - Taft, William Howard
- Inaugurations - Taylor, Zachery
- Inaugurations - Truman, Harry S.
- Inaugurations - Tyler, John
- Inaugurations - Washington, George
- Inaugurations - Wilson, Woodrow
- Incense Cedars
  See: Cemeteries - Rock Creek
- Independence Day
- Indians
- Industrial Research Building
- Interior Department Building
- Internal Revenue Service Building
- Interstate Commerce Commission Building
- Iron Works
  See: Streets - Water Street
- Islamic Center
- Iwo Jima Memorial
  See: Memorials - Iwo Jima
- Jail
- Jails
  See Also: Electric Chair
- Jefferson Memorial
  See: Memorials - Jefferson, Thomas; See: Tidal Basin
- Jewish Community Center
- Jews
- John Brown's Fort
  See: Potomac River
- John Marshall Place
- Journey Through Life
- Justice Department Building
- Kauffman Memorial
- Kemble Battery
  See: Civil War
- Kennedy Center
- Key Mansion
- Korean War
- L'Enfant Plaza
- Labor Department Building
- Lafayette Square
  See: Circles and Squares - Lafayette
- Langley Aerodrome
  See: Aviation - Langley
- League of Women Voters
- Libraries
  See Also: Public Library
- Library of Congress
- Library of Congress - Adams Building
- Library of Congress - Jefferson Building
- Library of Congress - Exterior
- Library of Congress - Fountain
- Library of Congress - Interior
- Library of Congress - Madison Building
- Lincoln Cottage
- Lincoln Memorial
  See: Memorials - Lincoln, Abraham (Memorial)
- Lockhouse
- Locks
- Mall, National
  See Also: Memorials - Lincoln, Abraham (Memorial); See Also: Weather; See Also: World War II - Temporary Buildings
- Maps
- Maps - 1700s
- Maps - 1800s
- Maps - 1900s
- March on Washington
  See: Parades - March on Washington
- Marine Corps Barracks
- Marine Corps Memorial
- Marines
  See: Music - Marine Corps Band
- Markets
  See Also: Fires
- Markets - Center Market
- Markets - Eastern Market
- Markets - New Center Market
- Markets - Open Air
- Markets - Western Market
- Martin Luther King Jr. Memorial Library
  See: Public Library
- Masonic Lodge
- Masonic Temple
  See: Halls, Masonic
- Mellon (Andrew W.) Auditorium
  See: Government Auditorium
- Memorials
- Memorials - Adams, Henry
- Memorials - Asbury, Francis
- Memorials - Barry, John
- Memorials - Bell, Alexander Graham
- Memorials - Bryan, William Jennings
- Memorials - Buchanan, James
- Memorials - Burke, Edmund
- Memorials - Butt-Millet
- Memorials - Churchill, Winston
- Memorials - Civil War Nurses
- Memorials - Columbus, Christopher
  See Also: Union Station; See Also: Visitors
- Memorials - Daguerre, Louis
- Memorials - Dante
- Memorials - D.A.R. Founders
- Memorials - Darlington, Joseph
- Memorials - Delano, Jane A.
- Memorials - Dupont, Samuel
- Memorials - Einstein, Albert
- Memorials - Ericsson, John
- Memorials - Extra Mile, The
- Memorials - Farragut, David
- Memorials - First Division, The
- Memorials - Franklin, Benjamin
- Memorials - Frederick The Great
- Memorials - Gallaudet, Thomas
- Memorials - Gallatin, Albert
- Memorials - Garfield, James
- Memorials - Gibbons, Cardinal James
- Memorials - Gompers, Samuel
- Memorials - Grant, Ulysses S.
- Memorials - Grand Army of the Republic
- Memorials - Greene, Nathaniel
- Memorials - Grief
- Memorials - Gross, Samuel
- Memorials - Hahnemann, Samuel
- Memorials - Hamilton, Alexander
- Memorials - Hancock, Winfield Scott
- Memorials - Henry, John
- Memorials - Iwo Jima
- Memorials - Jackson, Andrew
  See Also: White House
- Memorials - Japanese Lantern
- Memorials - Jefferson, Thomas
  See Also: Tidal Basin; See Also: Trees - Cherry
- Memorials - Joan of Arc
- Memorials - Johnson, Walter
- Memorials - Jones, John Paul
- Memorials - Kelly, Edward
- Memorials - Kosciuszo, Tadeusz
- Memorials - Lafayette, Gilbert de
- Memorials - Langley, Samuel P.
- Memorials - Liberty Brings Peace
- Memorials - Lincoln, Abraham (Memorial)
  See Also: Trees - Cherry; See Also: Visitors
- Memorials - Lincoln, Abraham (Statue)
- Memorials - Logan, John
- Memorials - Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth
- Memorials - Luther, Martin
- Memorials - Marine Corps Memorial
- Memorials - Marshall, John
- Memorials - McClellan, George
- Memorials - McPherson, James
- Memorials - Meade, George
- Memorials - Mercy
  See: Memorials - Delano, Jane A.
- Memorials - National Law Enforcement Officers Memorial
  See: Museums - National Building Museum
- Memorials - Naval Monument
- Memorials - Navy-Marine Memorial
- Memorials - Noyes, Crosby
- Memorials - Peace
- Memorials - Peace Cross
- Memorials - Pike, Albert
- Memorials - Pulaski, Casimir
- Memorials - Quoddy Project Demonstration
- Memorials - Rawlins, John
- Memorials - Rochambeau, Jean de
- Memorials - Roosevelt, Franklin D.
- Memorials - Roosevelt, Theodore
- Memorials - San Martin, Jose de
- Memorials - Second Division
- Memorials - Scott, Winfield
- Memorials - Shepherd, Alexander
- Memorials - Sheridan, Philip
- Memorials - Sherman, William T.
  See Also: Treasury Department
- Memorials - Spriggs, William
- Memorials - Steuben. Fredrick von
- Memorials - Straus, Oscar (Fountain)
- Memorials - Thomas, George
- Memorials - Titanic
  See Also: Memorials - Butt-Millet
- Memorials - Valor
- Memorials - Vietnam Veterans
- Memorials - Ward, Artemas
- Memorials - Washington, George (Masonic Temple)
- Memorials - Washington, George (Memorial Hall)
- Memorials - Washington, George (Monument)
  See Also: Memorials - Lincoln, Abraham (Memorial); See Also: Parks - Potomac; See Also: Tidal Basin; See Also: Treasury Department; See Also: Trees - Cherry; See Also: Weather; See Also: White House
- Memorials - Washington, George (Statues)
- Memorials - Watergate
- Memorials - Webster, Daniel
- Memorials - Witherspoon, John
- Memorials - World War I
- Memorials - World War II
- Metro Center
- Metropolitan Club
- Metropolitan District
  See Also: Alexandria, VA; See Also: Bladensburg, MD
- Metropolitan Police Boys Club
- Metropolitan Police Department
  See: Police Department
- Metropolitan Washington Board of Trade
- Military Drill
  See: Militia
- Militia
- Mills
  See Also: Weather
- Monuments
  See: Memorials
- Morgue
- Mosques
- Motion Pictures
  See: Television and Film
- Mount Vernon
- Municipal Building
  See: District Building
- Municipal Center
  See Also: City Hall; See Also: Courthouse; See Also: Streets - Pennsylvania Avenue
- Murals
- Museums
- Museums - General
- Museums - Air and Space
- Museums - American History
- Museums - Anacostia Neighborhood
- Museums - Dumbarton Oaks
- Museums - Hirshhorn
- Museums - National Building Museum
- Museums - National Gallery of Art
- Museums - National Portrait Gallery and Museum of American Art
- Museums - Natural History
- Music and Musical Groups
- Music and Musical Groups - General
- Music and Musical Groups - Marine Corps Band
- Music and Musical Groups - National Symphony Orchestra
- Music and Musical Groups - Navy Band
- Music and Musical Groups - Opera
- Music and Musical Groups - Watergate concerts
- National Academy of Science Building
- National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA) Building
- National Christmas Tree
- National Gallery of Art
  See: Art Gallery - National; See: Museums - National Gallery of Art; See: Fountains
- National Geographic Society
- National Mall
  See: Mall, National
- National Press Club
- National Symphony Orchestra
  See: Music - National Symphony
- Natural History Museum, National
  See: Museums - Natural History; See: Smithsonian Institution - Natural History
- Naval Observatory
- Navy, US
  See Also: Music - Navy Band
- Navy Department Buildings
  See Also: World War II Temporary Buildings; See Also: State, War and Navy Building
- Navy Yard
- Negros
  See: Blacks
- Netherlands Tower
  See: Carillons
- Newspapers
- Nightclubs
- Octagon House
  See: Houses - New York Avenue
- Old Age Homes
- Old Executive Office Building
  See: State, War and Navy Building
- Old Stone House
- Oldest Inhabitants Association
- Pan American Union Building
- Parades
  See Also: Inaugurations; See Also: Picketing, Protests and Demonstrations; See Also: Residential Sections - Adams Morgan
- Parades - General
- Parades - American Legion
- Parades - Army Day
- Parades - Blue Mass (Police Week)
- Parades - Cherry Blossom
- Parades - Civil Rights
- Parades - Civil War
- Parades - Civil War Centennial
- Parades - Dewey (Admiral)
- Parades - Eisenhower, Dwight D.
- Parades - Fire Department
- Parades - Grand Army of the Republic
- Parades - Home Rule
  See Also: Suffrage
- Parades - Knights of Pythias
- Parades - March on Washington
- Parades - Nimitz, Chester (Admiral)
- Parades - Prince Henry
- Parades - Roosevelt, Franklin D.
- Parades - Safety Patrol
- Parades - Shriner's
- Parades - Suffrage
- Parades - Truman, Harry S.
- Parades - Wainwright, (General)
- Parades - World War I
  See Also: World War I
- Parades - World War II
- Parks
  See Also: Trees - Cherry; See Also: Tidal Basin; See Also: Mall, National; See Also: Mills
- Parks - General
- Parks - Anacostia
- Parks - Fort Reno
- Parks - Franklin
- Parks - Garfield
- Parks - Hains Point
- Parks - Lafayette
- Parks - Lincoln
- Parks - Lord Bryce
- Parks - Meridian Hill
- Parks - Mitchell
- Parks - Pershing
  See: Circles and Squares - Pershing Square
- Parks - Potomac Park
- Parks - President's
  See: White House
- Parks - Pulaski
- Parks - Rawlins
- Parks - Rock Creek
  See Also: Streets - Rock Creek Parkway; See Also: Weather; See Also: Zoo
- Patent Office
- Pension Office
- Pentagon
  See Also: War Department; See Also: Subways
- People
- Peoples Drug Store
  See: Stores - Peoples Drug Store
- PEPCO
  See: Electricity
- Pharmacy
- Picketing, Protests and Demonstrations
  See Also: Parades - Civil Rights; See Also: Parades - Home Rule; See Also: Parades - March on Washington; See Also: Parades - Suffrage; See Also: Suffrage
- Picketing, Protests and Demonstrations - General
- Picketing, Protests and Demonstrations - Anti-War
- Picketing, Protests and Demonstrations - Bonus Army
- Picketing, Protests and Demonstrations - Civil Rights
- Picketing, Protests and Demonstrations - Poor Peoples Campaign
- Picketing, Protests and Demonstrations - Pierce Mill
  See: Mills
- Picketing, Protests and Demonstrations - Playgrounds
- Picketing, Protests and Demonstrations - Police Department
- Picketing, Protests and Demonstrations - Politics and Government
- Picketing, Protests and Demonstrations - Poor Peoples Campaign
- Portrait Gallery
  See: Patent Office; See: Museums - National Portrait Gallery
- Post Office
- Post Office - General
- Post Office - F Street
- Post Office - Federal Triangle
- Post Office - Massachusetts Avenue
- Post Office - Pennsylvania Avenue
  See Also: Streets-Pennsylvania Avenue; See Also: Transportation
- Potomac Canal
  See: Canals
- Potomac Electric Power Company (PEPCO)
- Potomac River
  See Also: Floods; See Also: Boats; See Also: Waterfront
- General
- Boats and Boating
- Floods
- Great Falls
- President of the United States (in DC)
  See Also: White House; See Also: Biographical A-Z
- President's Park
- Prisons
- Private Schools
- Private Schools - Arlington Hall
- Private Schools - Army and Navy Preparatory
- Private Schools - Belcourt Seminary
- Private Schools - Bliss Electrical School
- Private Schools - Bristol School
- Private Schools - Burr's School
- Private Schools - Capitol Page School
- Private Schools - Cathedral Hall School
- Private Schools - Chenoweth School
- Private Schools - Chevy Chase School for Girls
- Private Schools - Columbia Tech
- Private Schools - Dupont Girls School
- Private Schools - Dupont Seminary
- Private Schools - Fairmont Seminary
- Private Schools - Gonzaga